http://www.ekmcconkey.com/privacy-policy/

Call 717-755-9266
Privacy Policy Please review this information carefully.
Our privacy policy.
Important information for your use of our website.
As a current client of E.K. McConkey & Co., Inc./McConkey Benefits & Financial Services, LLC, we would like to take this opportunity to both thank you for your business and share McConkey’s intentions for protecting the privacy of information that we gather from you and your employees.
We place a high value on the confidentiality of your personal information and please note that McConkey does not share your information with any unaffiliated third party. We feel so strongly about this that our employee manual states the following: “You are expected to handle ALL INFORMATION regarding our clients and our agency with the strictest of confidentiality. Our clients are our future. Information regarding our clients and our agency business is never to be discussed with any unauthorized party outside of our agency.”
The information we collect is necessary for us to adequately help meet your insurance and benefits needs and is usually required before an insurance company will evaluate your risk. We also expect the insurance companies that we represent to be compliant with privacy laws. We use a secure internet and e-mail provider to protect the confidentiality of electronic communications.
The information we collect falls into several categories:
Information received from you on applications and other forms
Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others
Information we receive from a credit reporting agency
Information we receive from a medical information bureau
Information from other sources such as from the government or your employer
Again, we appreciate your business, and in order to continue building upon that relationship, we believe it is necessary, not only from a legal standpoint, but also as a sound business practice, that our clients understand the importance of how we handle your personal and private information. McConkey will continue to monitor the effectiveness of this privacy policy in accordance with applicable state and federal laws.
Here to Help
717-755-9266
info@ekmcconkey.com
Quick LinksClient Portal
McConkey 24/7
Report a Claim
Request Policy Change
Request Certificate
Or, Contact Us
About McConkey Insurance & Benefits We’re an independent insurance agency offering a comprehensive suite of insurance solutions to protect your business and your life from the unexpected.
We don’t just sell insurance. We work closely with clients to help them make important and informed decisions every day when it comes to protection and their future.
WEBSITE ACCESSIBILITY INFORMATION
Contact us We’re here when you need us most.
Call, email or stop by.
(Monday – Friday, 8AM – 5PM ET)
Join our mailing list
Email*
This field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Join Now
© 2020 McConkey Insurance & Benefits.
All rights reserved. | Privacy PolicyPowered by Forge3 ActiveAgency.
